Yo! Crackheads! Woo!
I guess they know we’re coming.
Alright, that’s the block right here.
Be cool, don’t… you know.
What?
Err, nothing.
Yo, what the fuck?
Yo, what's up? Y’all tryna smoke?
No. Y’all know Boobie?
Boobie, huh? Yeah, he ain’t here, though.
Well, we're picking something up for him.
You know anything about that?
Yeah. Go inside and ask for Raymond, bruh.
Appreciate it.
Like, might have to fuck around
and shake some shit, know I’m saying?
Eh, fo sho. Yeah, yeah. Mmm hmm.
Man… I don't even wanna hear that shit.
- Hey.
- Man… I don't even wanna hear that shit.
- Like, I don't even wanna hear that shit.
Like, I don't even wanna hear that shit.
Hold up, bruh.
Yo. Ya’ll need something?
Raymond?
Nah. Whatchu want?
Boobie sent us for a pickup.
Aight, aight.
Yo! We going up.
Right inside.
You said you was here for a pickup or a drop off?
Pick up.
Straight up, first door on the right.
Yep.
How you doing, big guy?
Buddy…
This has gotta be the door, right?
Looks like it.
What you want?
Yo, is Raymond around?
Nah, never heard of him.
Yo, we’re here to pick up. For Boobie.
Aight, hold up.
Yo, Ray! These two say they’re for Boobie.
I already told that motherfucker what the fuck going on, man.
He seriously sent y’all over here right now?
We’re just here to collect, man.
Why he ain’t come to collect?
You ain’t ask yourselves that?
No.
Look, we could go back empty handed.
My partner's off the grid right now, you feel me?
Until I figure out where the fuck he at
and what the fuck going on
we in a holding pattern right here.
So Boobie knows all this, right?
Yeah, he fucking knows.
Problem is he only worried about himself.
Yo, phone.
Let me tell y’all something,
at this point I really don’t give a fuck.
Ay, pack that shit up.
Yo Ray, it’s him. Ernesto.
Put it on speakerphone.
Raymond.
Yo, Nesto!
Raymond, Raymond.
Where the fuck you at?
Óyeme, mi hermano, we got a situation happening.
Our friends on the task force are on their way.
They say they’re paying you a visit
so just let them take whatever they want, okay?
What the fuck you talking about?
You know I got a nigga outside yo momma house, right?
Raymond, listen very closely, cabrón.
Raymond.
The fuck is that?
Hey, yo, Ray! It’s twelve! They tooled up and everything!
Raymond?
Let’s get these workers out of here, man!
Ah, shit!
- Wrong way, this way.
- Ah, shit!
Wrong way, this way.
Come on, come on!
Move, move!
I always been there for you.
But this what I get?
Police! Don't fucking move!
It is what it is, my friend.
Holy shit!
Stay down!
Yeah, I know.
Come on, we need to find a way out.
I got Boobie’s bricks.
Fuck Boobie! We gotta get out of this.
Lu, push up. Stay with me.
Lu, cover!
- On it!
- Lu, cover!
What the fuck is going on here?!
Fuck, it’s him!
Can’t you fucking handle a bunch of street pushers?
Hey man, this ain’t even loaded!
Aww, too bad!
Clean this shit up!
It’s fucking Méndez!
Yep. You think he saw us?
No. He couldn’t have.
Oh, coño.
Yo, they got more cops coming in from downstairs.
Get in here ‘fore they get yo ass!
Thanks, man.
Wh- Raymond, what’s going. What the fuck going on?
What the fuck y’all doing in here?
You ain’t hear all that outside? Now, now just hold on a minute.
"Hold on"? You got motherfuckers running up in my house.
You are not allowed to just come in here.
Every time I try to find some peace it’s something else!
And that’s my fault?
My AC! Don’t you climb out my motherfucking window!
Aunt Tee! C’mon now!
- Easy. Shit!
- Aunt Tee! C’mon now!
Easy. Shit!
Hey.
Hey, Jay.
I bought these. What do you think?
I can buy my own clothes, you know.
Sure you can. But would they look that good?
Yeah, yeah. Okay.
You know Brian wants us there for cocktails.
Uh-huh.
You know what you’re gonna wear yet?
Relax, Jay.
Okay, which do you think?
Uhh… sequins?
Sequins?
Okay, the other one.
You know, what you're wearing right now
looks pretty good, so… You wanna head out?
I don’t wanna be late.
Yeah, alright. Just gimme a few seconds.
Does life feel hopeless?
Are you constantly searching for a way out?
Luckily for you, those days are over thanks to Angstipan!
Ah, the great outdoors. Nature’s playground.
A carnival of infinite possibilities.
Overflowing with creatures great and small.
Magnificent and proud.
Hungry?
Not anymore.
Mouthwatering meats from the open range
topped off with our world famous buns.
Ready.
Damn. Worth the wait.
Here we go, finally.
Okay, you’re wound up a little tight. What’s up?
Nothing, I just don’t like being late.
We’re not that late.
Brian’s doing us a favor, you know?
We need this intro, Lu.
I get it.
You know, we’re in some deep fucking shit.
I get that too.
Who is this guy?
You know, besides Brian’s old cellmate.
I know as much as you.
Cal might have said he was like former
Dominican intelligence or something.
Damn.
What?
Just kinda wish we weren’t running late.
Really, huh?
What? I didn’t know all this.
Relationships are about communication, Jay.
Sure, yeah I’m sorry.
Where you at, Vice City girls?
Fuck, oh no! Argh-uh!
What did I fucking say?
What the hell are you doing?
You seeing this?
Well look who's back.
What?
Sometimes I’m just more comfortable
when I have to use a gun, you know?
Just be charming, 'kay?
Yeah.
And don’t worry about Brian. Dude’s retired.
I mean, look at Lori’s Snapmatic. Looks like they’re loving it.
There they are. At the bar.
Oh my god, as I live and breathe. Look at the two of you.
Hey, Lori. It’s good to see you, Brian.
Uh huh.
Oh, c’mere, give us a hug.
I told Brian, I thought you two were both dead for sure.
Now, what have you gotten yourselves into?
I wanna know everything.
I don’t know what this is.
Look, I was just sightseeing with my girl.
Do tourists carry these?
You fucking…
- Shut up!
- You fucking…
Hold on.
This is so fucked!
Well, Brian was quite the stud back in the day.
Was?!
Wait…
What’s up?
That job, it has to be done tonight.
Tonight?
He wants it on the quiet. He only wants one of you.
Well.
You know.
I don't mind.
I mean, I…
If you wanted to.
I’m gonna go.
Enjoy your dinner, guys. I’ll be back for dessert.
Well, I’ll walk you out, I need the ladies.
Yeah, let’s take in the view.
I never get to smoke these in front of Lori.
I ever tell you about uh… the uh, fairground that
rolled into my home town when I was a kid?
I don’t think so.
They had bale mazes and Ferris wheel.
Hell, it was the highlight of the god damn summer for us kids.
Everybody, hands where we can see them!
And they had this beautiful carousel.
One night we snuck in and a buddy of mine, he got it working.
Look what the law chased in.
The locals are feisty!
Leonida, baby.
Then he cranked the speed up so fast we thought we was flying.
What now?
It started going faster and faster and
it was getting harder to hold on and I said "well shit".
"That ain’t good".
Get down!
- Watch out!
- Get down!
- And I fucking jumped.
And I fucking jumped.
Jimmy Canto stayed on.
Cracked his head open. Died that night.
You got a point?
Yeah, yeah. You gotta know when to get off, Jason.
You hear me?
Oh. Let's head back.
Hey.
Hey. Got this Raul guy’s car and
heading to the address he gave.
Nice. On my way.
Yo, so I’ve been thinking, and
I don’t think we should tell him about,
you know, our troubles. Not just yet.
Thought that was the whole point of this?
Look, he could sell us out.
Or put a bullet through our heads.
I mean seriously,
what reason do we have to trust this guy?
Alright, so how you wanna play it?
Slow play. Just say,
"Hi, nice to meet you. Here's your car."
"Where's our payment?" "Please let us know
about any further criminal opportunities."
Ok. See you there.
Yep.
You miss me?
I’ve been busy. You gonna text this guy?
Dude could be a cop for all we know.
He’s not a cop, alright? He’s just cautious.
It’s probably why he survived so long. We could learn something.
Maybe you could.
Yeah, you’re the perfect criminal.
Jason? Lucia?
Yeah.
We gotta go.
Go?
Yeah, go. Like, right fucking now.
What you think I needed a lift for?
Shit. He’s cautious alright.
In Spanish: Go, go! Goddamn psycho,
show me what kinda driver you are!
Hey, bro, get your ass back here man.
Huh?
Come on, you gotta hold these fuckers off.
I got a little something for you to play with.
Here, you take this.
It’s getting crowded here.
I’m going to punch through to the freeway!
Negative. Stay local.
Ok.
Jay, hang on!
Don’t get us trapped in here, Lu!
No, no, no. This is good. Keep cutting through.
Back up into this alley here.
Ok.
That’s it. Good. Ahora we just chill here for a minute.
Fuckin’ shit show.
You want me to take the wheel?
What? No.
Look, you think everything always
goes as planned, huh? No, mami, no.
There will always be some kind of bullshit.
A professional adapts. Are you a professional, Lucia, hm?
Of course.
Good, I need a professional.
In Spanish: Shit…
I see him.
I think he saw us too. Let’s go!
In Spanish: Let's go!
Move! Move it!
Is this fucking real now?
Shit. Don’t have eyes on suspect’s vehicle.
Okay, out. Don’t leave anything in here.
Alright, Jason, we’re cargo.
Copy.
Maybe some warning next time?
What should I tell you, to put it in your calendar?
Friday morning, bank robbery. Come on.
We pass the test?
You did fine. We’re still alive.
This could be the start of, uh, something good.
Keep your phones on.
In Spanish: Oh, mamita! So nice to see you!
Oh hey.
Take me to the loot, baby. I need to see it!
Does this mean we’re in his crew?
Yeah, I think so.
You think he can help us?
We don’t have any better ideas, do we?
Where are we?
Back in Bayside.
Wanna take a look around?
Elbows in tight, you wanna thrust!
Oh y-yeah!
Yo, Jay! What’s happening, baby?
- Yo…
- Yo, Jay! What’s happening, baby?
Yo, Jay! What’s happening, baby?
What’s up, man?
Loony! What's up, girl?
Ass up! Booty, booty, booty, twerk!
Just try to keep it clean.
To hell with you!
Hey! I’m watching you.
Cops are on their way.
Oh shit! Who the fuck are you?
What the fuck is this?
Oh, the trunk challenge!
Wait, did you steal my friend’s car?
Yeah.
Holy shit, chat! What do I do?
Jesus.
Look, look, look, look, look. Look.
The actual cops are chasing us.
I bet you’d be real good at battle rapping, dog.
Oh, yeah?
Lucia, Jason. Come take a seat.
I’m waiting on the ETA for the flight.
Can I get you anything?
Tea, coffee, champagne?
Three more champagnes. Thank you.
Be right back.
Trust me, a slight buzz will only help you.
So Val, I know it’s a party but we are working, right?
The job is Andrés de León. Protect him but keep him in line.
Gas him up. Boost his ego. Make him feel good about himself.
Babysit.
Mhm.
Hey! There is a sight for sore eyes. Tina! What’s up, chula?
Andrés! It's been forever, how is everything?
Ah, man, it’s been non-stop.
Lucia, Jason. Please meet Andrés de León.
Sorry guys, I’m a hugger. I’m a hugger, come in here, get in here!
Oh.
Yes! Alright!
Beautiful, beautiful, yes. Gorgeous! Alright, strong. Good job.
Should we go, gentlemen?
I guess you're the driver?
- Sure.
- I guess you're the driver?
- Alright, let’s go.
Alright, let’s go.
Ah, c’mon.
Alright. We’re good.
Ah fuck it, you ready for this party bro?
I don’t know, maybe.
Alright.
What do you mean "maybe"?
I’m ready for a party
I don’t know about this party.
Oh shit, okay.
Hey driver, what was your name again?
In Spanish: Assholes! We're coming!
Alright.
Here we go.
Woo!
Welcome. How was your flight, sir?
Yeah, yeah, real good time!
Hey, those waitresses were all NDA’d, yeah?
The flight attendants? Yes, of course.
NDA after the fact? That’s a rookie move, bro.
And you guys got our room sorted?
Yes, it’s all ready for you.
24th floor executive conference room.
Perfect! Let’s go freshen up, bro.
Let’s do it!
Hey, honey, so a couple of Elonzo’s producer friends are in town
and we’re gonna do a deep dive into my creative roadmap.
So, we’ll be up in the conference room doing a little business hang
you know, think-tank stuff. 'Kay?
Seriously? Right now?
Yeah, baby, you snooze you lose!
In Spanish: Unbelievable.
Petra, can I introduce you to Andrés’ new security detail?
Jason and Lucia, this is Petra Navarro, COO of Megamundo.
- Yes, good.
- Jason and Lucia, this is Petra Navarro, COO of Megamundo.
Yes, good.
Can I take you up?
Yes, please. Let’s go. I don’t want
to spend the whole night in the lobby.
Let him do what he does, then I want him down here, ok?
You got it.
In Spanish: Evening, ladies.
Gustavo, I want you to meet Lucia.
She’s part of the new security detail that we hired for Andrés.
Some security guy just took my guns.
It’s a good thing you’re good with your hands.
These guys seem to have it covered. We should be fine.
Okay.
Do it bro! Do it, do it, do it!
Here I come!
A private meeting. Don’t come in!
Hey, Andrés.
Whoa whoa, hey hey, its ok it’s ok,
he’s my guy it’s my guy it’s my guy.
Hey, buddy. Just uh, haha, christening the new building.
Hey, man.
Oh, sorry to interrupt.
Aye, man can you run and get us a bottle of tequila,
some sparkling water, a few beers you know
just a selection of shit to drink, yeah? Thanks, buddy. Yeah.
Uh huh, so they just called and
asked me to bring you down to the party now.
Petra wants you. There’s some big speech happening.
No! No fuck, fuck that shit. Ha, fuck that.
- Yeah, sorry no. Hard pass, man. We’re on a roll here, you know.
- No! No fuck, fuck that shit. Ha, fuck that.
Yeah, sorry no. Hard pass, man. We’re on a roll here, you know.
Frontal cortex is in overdrive, I mean, how many
ideas did I just have in the last five minutes, bro?
So many, bro, so fucking many.
It’s like the band is back together
and I just met these fucking guys.
C’mon, guys.
Hello, everyone.
I just want to thank you all for coming here
tonight to join us in celebrating the opening
of Megamundo’s first corporate headquarters on American soil.
We all did this together. As a family.
The party’s over!
Everybody! On the ground! Now!
In Spanish: What the hell?
Protect the asset.
In Spanish: Shit!
Move, move, move! Move, move, move, move!
Move!
Hey, hey, hey, hey! Give me the phone.
Who am I going to call? I’m not stupid.
Sup, guys. How’s it going down there?
Who the fuck is this?
We’ll talk more later, okay?
In Spanish: What the fuck?
In Spanish: We got a problem.
In Spanish: Shit, shit, grenade!
Nice distraction, Jay. A bit dramatic.
You're welcome. Going upstairs. He’s got Andrés.
Shit, okay. On my way.
Lu? Lu? Fuck.
In Spanish: Motherfucker, fucking fuck!
Not the face, man! Not the face!
Where’s the money?
I don't know!
- Where’s the fucking money?
- I don't know!
Where’s the fucking money?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait! Ahhh!
I don't know, man! They don't tell me shit!
Ughhhh!
Jay dog!
Ahhhggg!!
Hurts, right? Try wearing them, bitch.
In Spanish: I don't think so, bitch!
Ah, shit!
Might not feel like it but these are your glory days.
The salad years, you know?
Nothing is going to beat who you are now.
You can’t see all the fucked up shit that’s looming on the horizon.
Enjoy this, dude.
If this right now was all that there is…
all the time.
It would be perfect.
Trust me.